<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Customer Service on ITSthe1 - IT &amp; Telecom Solutions</title><link>https://www.itsthe1.com/tags/customer-service/</link><description>Recent content in Customer Service on ITSthe1 - IT &amp; Telecom Solutions</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.itsthe1.com/tags/customer-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1.Hotel - Guest Engagement &amp; Experience Platform</title><link>https://www.itsthe1.com/products/hospitality-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.itsthe1.com/products/hospitality-app/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>1.Hotel by ITSthe1 Solutions&lt;/strong> is a guest-facing application designed to elevate the hospitality experience across hotels, hospitals, resorts, and serviced apartments. Delivered as a &lt;strong>WebApp or native mobile app (iOS &amp;amp; Android)&lt;/strong>, it enables real-time guest interaction, service automation, and property engagement.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The solution is &lt;strong>fully integrated with our 1.TV platform&lt;/strong>, using a shared backend system to deliver consistent content across TV and mobile. It also works seamlessly with &lt;strong>1.Support (1.SUP)&lt;/strong>, our staff-facing app, ensuring every guest request is actioned through an automated support ticket workflow.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>1.Support - Smart Support Ticketing &amp; Workflow Automation</title><link>https://www.itsthe1.com/products/helpdesk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.itsthe1.com/products/helpdesk/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>1.Support by ITSthe1 Solutions&lt;/strong> is a centralized support ticketing and workflow management system designed for hotels, hospitals, resorts, MDUs, universities, corporate offices, and service-based enterprises. Whether used independently or &lt;strong>fully integrated with our 1.TV (in-room entertainment system) and 1.Hotel (guest mobile app)&lt;/strong>, it enables real-time ticket creation, SLA-based task tracking, multi-level escalation, and operational performance analytics across departments with comprehensive reporting to monitor Key Performance Indicators (KPIs).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Transform your service operations with intelligent automation, seamless integrations, and data-driven insights that enhance both staff efficiency and customer satisfaction.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>